<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Message Manager</title>
    <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager" />
    <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Gerco Dries</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Message Manager 3.2 released</title>
        <author>
            <name>Gerco Dries</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/message-manager-32-released.html"/>
        <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/message-manager-32-released.html</id>

        <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Changes in this version: If you are already running version 3.1, your application will automatically upgrade. If not, click&nbsp;run Message Manager 3.2&nbsp;to download and run the new version. 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Changes in this version:</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul>
<li>New code signing certificate, you may have to accept some warnings again to install this version.</li>
<li><a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager/issues/52/not-possible-to-save-multi-part-sonicmq-q">#52</a> Automatically create directory if it doesn't exist when saving multipart messages.</li>
<li>Added support for saving JSON payloads</li>
</ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>If you are already running version 3.1, your application will automatically upgrade. If not, click&nbsp;<a href="https://queuemanager.nl/app/MessageManager.jnlp">run Message Manager 3.2</a>&nbsp;to download and run the new version.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Message Manager 3.1 released</title>
        <author>
            <name>Gerco Dries</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/message-manager-31-released.html"/>
        <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/message-manager-31-released.html</id>

        <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    It's been a while since I released a new version, but here is version 3.1 of Message Manager. It contains the following changes: If you are already running version 3.0, your application will automatically upgrade. If not, click run Message Manager 3.1 to download and run the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>It's been a while since I released a new version, but here is version 3.1 of Message Manager. It contains the following changes:</p>
<ul>
 	
<li>Support for <a href="https://www.solace.com">Solace</a> messaging</li>
<li>There is now a search box that allows you search through message headers, properties, message body and all parts of a SonicMQ multi-part message. (#35)</li>
<li>There is a Swing Look and Feel selector in the settings tab (requires restart)</li>
<li>Fix display of large message sizes in queues table (#22)</li>
<li>Added JMSPriority field to message sender</li>
</ul>
<p>
If you are already running version 3.0, your application will automatically upgrade. If not, click <a href="https://queuemanager.nl/app/MessageManager.jnlp">run Message Manager 3.1</a> to download and run the new version.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Support for Solace messaging is now available in the nightly build</title>
        <author>
            <name>Gerco Dries</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/support-for-solace-messaging-is-now-available-in-the-nightly-build.html"/>
        <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/support-for-solace-messaging-is-now-available-in-the-nightly-build.html</id>

        <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    The nightly build of Message Manager now has support for Solace messaging. Please give it a try if you are interested. This is a very early version of the Solace support and it will have bugs, probably many. Click here to run MessageManager 3.1-SNAPSHOT To be&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The nightly build of Message Manager now has support for <a href="http://www.solace.com">Solace</a> messaging. Please give it a try if you are interested. This is a very early version of the Solace support and it will have bugs, probably many.</p>
<p>Click here to run <a href="/v3/nightly/app/MessageManager.jnlp">MessageManager 3.1-SNAPSHOT</a></p>
<p>To be safe, make a backup of your configuration file for safety, you can find that in the following location depending on your operating system:</p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<th>Operating System</th>
<th>Location</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Windows</td>
<td>%APPDATA%\MessageManager\config.xml</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Mac OS X</td>
<td>~/Library/Application Support/MessageManager/config.xml</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Linux</td>
<td>~/.config/MessageManager/config.xml</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>
If you have previously installed a nightly build, please refer to the above table and delete the "plugins/3.1-SNAPSHOT" directory in that same location before running this new build. The naming of the plugin jar files has changed and there may be conflicts if you have had previous versions installed.</p>
<p>When you find any bugs, please <a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager/issues/new">report them</a>.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Multi-MQ Message Manager 3.0 is now available</title>
        <author>
            <name>Gerco Dries</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/multi-mq-message-manager-30-is-now-available.html"/>
        <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/multi-mq-message-manager-30-is-now-available.html</id>

        <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    The multi MQ version of Message Manager 3.0 is now available, this version supports both SonicMQ and ActiveMQ. Click to run Message Manager 3.0 In order to use this application: This version is a separate download and will not overwrite any of the other versions you may&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The multi MQ version of Message Manager 3.0 is now available, this version supports both SonicMQ and ActiveMQ.</p>
<p>Click to run <a href="http://queuemanager.nl/app/MessageManager.jnlp">Message Manager 3.0</a></p>
<p>In order to use this application:</p>
<ol>
 	
<li>Select the profile you want to use by clicking it in the list on the left</li>
<li>Edit the profile by providing a name and set a classpath for your messaging system</p>
<ul>
 	
<li>for Sonic MQ 7.0 or later select any jar (for example sonic_Client.jar) in the MQ/lib directory and the other required jars will be selected automatically</li>
<li>for ActiveMQ 5.11 or later select the activemq-all jar file in your ActiveMQ installation</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Click the "Activate Profile" button in the lower right corner of the window</li>
</ol>
<p>
This version is a separate download and will not overwrite any of the other versions you may have installed. Please provide any and all feedback on issues or improvements in the comments or by <a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager/issues/new">filing an issue</a> on Bitbucket.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>First multi MQ test version available</title>
        <author>
            <name>Gerco Dries</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/first-multi-mq-test-version-available.html"/>
        <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/first-multi-mq-test-version-available.html</id>

        <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I have just uploaded the first test build of the multi MQ version of Message Manager. This version supports both SonicMQ and ActiveMQ. Message Manager 3.0-SNAPSHOT In order to use this application: This version is a separate download and will not overwrite any of the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I have just uploaded the first test build of the multi MQ version of Message Manager. This version supports both SonicMQ and ActiveMQ.</p>
<p><a href="http://queuemanager.nl/v3/nightly/app/MessageManager.jnlp">Message Manager 3.0-SNAPSHOT</a></p>
<p>In order to use this application:</p>
<ol>
	
<li>Select the profile you want to use by clicking it in the list on the left</li>
<li>Edit the profile by providing a name and set a classpath for your messaging system</p>
<ul>
	
<li>for Sonic MQ 7.0 or later select any jar (for example sonic_Client.jar) in the MQ/lib directory and the other required jars will be selected automatically</li>
<li>for ActiveMQ 5.11 or later select the activemq-all jar file in your ActiveMQ installation</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Click the "Activate Profile" button in the lower right corner of the window</li>
</ol>
<p>
This version is a separate download and will not overwrite any of the other versions you may have installed. Please provide any and all feedback on issues or improvements in the comments or by <a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager/issues/new">filing an issue</a> on Bitbucket.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>New code signing certificate</title>
        <author>
            <name>Gerco Dries</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/new-code-signing-certificate.html"/>
        <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/new-code-signing-certificate.html</id>

        <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Starting today, the nightly builds will be signed with a new certificate. This may cause a warning or prompt to reverify that you want to run software signed with the new certificate. The latest release build is still signed with the old certificate and will&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Starting today, the nightly builds will be signed with a new certificate. This may cause a warning or prompt to reverify that you want to run software signed with the new certificate. The latest release build is still signed with the old certificate and will stay that way until the next release.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>First Message Manager 3.0 Beta is available</title>
        <author>
            <name>Gerco Dries</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/first-message-manager-30-beta-is-available.html"/>
        <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/first-message-manager-30-beta-is-available.html</id>

        <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I've been working on Message Manager 3.0, which will replace the 2.x branch Sonic Message Manager in time. This will be a separate download and will not automatically upgrade from 2.x versions for technical reasons. There are major changes in the application, but most of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I've been working on Message Manager 3.0, which will replace the 2.x branch Sonic Message Manager in time. This will be a separate download and will not automatically upgrade from 2.x versions for technical reasons. There are major changes in the application, but most of those are invisible to the users:</p>
<ul>
	
<li>Internal refactoring that allows for a plugin system in the near future. It will be possible to create and install plugins for custom message formats, other messaging systems, new UI tabs and more.</li>
<li>Syntax highlighting XML editor/viewer</li>
<li>Faster download due to Pack200 compression, it's now less than 3MB to download.</li>
<li>Java 6 is now required</li>
<li>Support for Sonic 6.1 was dropped</li>
<li>Support for Sonic 2015 was added</li>
</ul>
<p>
The first beta version of 3.0 is available for download here. These versions will automatically update to the latest code on a nightly basis and should be considered unstable.</p>
<ul>
	
<li><a href="/v3/nightly/7.0/SonicMessageManager.jnlp">Message Manager for Sonic MQ 7.0 NIGHTLY</a></li>
<li><a href="/v3/nightly/7.5/SonicMessageManager.jnlp">Message Manager for Sonic MQ 7.5 NIGHTLY</a></li>
<li><a href="/v3/nightly/7.6/SonicMessageManager.jnlp">Message Manager for Sonic MQ 7.6 NIGHTLY</a></li>
<li><a href="/v3/nightly/8.0/SonicMessageManager.jnlp">Message Manager for Sonic MQ 8.0 NIGHTLY</a></li>
<li><a href="/v3/nightly/8.5/SonicMessageManager.jnlp">Message Manager for Sonic MQ 8.5 NIGHTLY</a></li>
<li><a href="/v3/nightly/8.6/SonicMessageManager.jnlp">Message Manager for Sonic MQ 2013 NIGHTLY</a></li>
<li><a href="/v3/nightly/10.0/SonicMessageManager.jnlp">Message Manager for Sonic MQ 2015 NIGHTLY</a></li>
</ul>
<p>
The <a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager">source code</a> for this version is available on Bitbucket, please <a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager/issues/new">report any issues here</a>.</p>
<p>Future versions of Message Manager 3.0 will no longer be specific to a particular version of Sonic MQ. At that time, you will have to download a new version of the application.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Nightly Builds Signed With New Certificate</title>
        <author>
            <name>Gerco Dries</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/nightly-builds-signed-with-new-certificate.html"/>
        <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/nightly-builds-signed-with-new-certificate.html</id>

        <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I've obtained a new code signing certificate and used it to sign the nightly builds. Since this is a new certificate, you may see error messages if Java Web Start was unable to update all downloaded files at once. If you get a message stating&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I've obtained a new code signing certificate and used it to sign the nightly builds. Since this is a new certificate, you may see error messages if Java Web Start was unable to update all downloaded files at once. If you get a message stating that "Not all files are signed with the same certificate" or "The signed version does not match the downloaded version", clear your Java Web Start cache and try again.</p>
<p>In rare cases, Java Web Start may get stuck and there is no way to fix it. In that case, you will have to resort the stable builds or offline installation for 24h to give Java Web Start some time to realize that it needs to update the rest of the files.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sonic Message Manager 2.6 Released</title>
        <author>
            <name>Gerco Dries</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/sonic-message-manager-26-released.html"/>
        <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/sonic-message-manager-26-released.html</id>

        <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Sonic Message Manager 2.6 has just been released. The changes in this version are: Please give it a try and let me know of any issues. Special thanks to Sujeeth Nayak and Romeu Flores for contributing code to this release. 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Sonic Message Manager 2.6 has just been released. The changes in this version are:</p>
<ul>
	
<li>Queue names are now sorted for equal numbers of messages (<a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager-2.x/issue/1/sorting-queue-names">Bitbucket issue #1</a>)</li>
<li>JMS Properties are now easier to copy (<a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager-2.x/issue/2/copying-message-properties">Bitbucket issue #2</a>)</li>
<li>JMS Properties are now sorted by name (<a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager-2.x/issue/3/sorting-message-properties-by-name">Bitbucket issue #3</a>)</li>
<li>.esbmsg files now supports saving/loading of Content-ID headers (<a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager-2.x/issue/4/loading-a-esbmsg-file-does-not-populate">Bitbucket issue #4</a>)</li>
<li>Added release notes/message of the day banner for announcements</li>
</ul>
<p>
Please give it a try and let me know of any <a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager-2.x/issues/new">issues</a>. Special thanks to Sujeeth Nayak and Romeu Flores for contributing code to this release.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Source code moved to Bitbucket</title>
        <author>
            <name>Gerco Dries</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/source-code-moved-to-bitbucket.html"/>
        <id>https://gerco.github.io/messagemanager/source-code-moved-to-bitbucket.html</id>

        <updated>2022-02-21T18:13:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    To resolve issues with people trying to get access to the source code of Sonic Message Manager, I moved it to Bitbucket. I'm also using their issue tracker now instead of using a local instance of Trac. This means that the source code is now&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>To resolve issues with people trying to get access to the source code of Sonic Message Manager, I moved it to Bitbucket. I'm also using their issue tracker now instead of using a local instance of Trac. This means that the source code is now available at:</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager-2.x">https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager-2.x</a></p>
<p>And the issue tracker is available at:</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager-2.x/issues">https://bitbucket.org/gerco/messagemanager-2.x/issues</a></p>
<p>I copied all open issues from the old Trac database to the Bitbucket issue tracker. Since this was a manual process, I may have missed some information and some triage will need to be done to make sure all is ok.</p>
<p>Please create any missing issues, fork, code and create pull requests as you see fit.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
